Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files, 1885-2008 and undated, bulk 1920-1995 RL.00658
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files
1885-2008 and undated bulk 1920-1995
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.00658
400 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. The JWT Account Files spans the years 1885-2007, with the bulk of materials covering 1920-1995. It is an artificially-created collection of information about client accounts held by the JWT and provides information about JWT's management of its advertising campaigns. Additionally, the files document deliberations about such topics as media selection; markets and marketing; and target audience for individual advertising campaigns. The bulk of the materials, especially the older records, document clients managed by JWT's New York Office, but the work of other offices is also represented, including: Atlanta Office (Marine Corps); Chicago Office (Oscar Mayer, Kraft); Detroit Office (Ford); and San Francisco Office (Sprint). The collection includes account histories; research reports; memoranda; correspondence; printed material; clippings; brochures and pamphlets; product labels and packaging designs; original artwork and advertising proofs; slides; photographs; audiocassettes and videocassettes. Clients represented include Eastman Kodak; Ford; Ford Dealer Association; R.T. French; General Cigar; Hamm's beer; Handy Andy; International Banana Association; IBM; Kellogg; Kraft; Quaker Oats; U.S. Marine Corps; US Sprint; Warner Lambert; White Castle; and the 1964 World's Fair. More limited materials are available for other significant JWT clients, including: Burger King; Champion Spark Plug; Domino's Pizza; Lever Brothers; Northern Telecom; Oscar Mayer; Rolex; Standard Brands; and Scott Paper. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
28,0000 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted.
Original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
Unpublished materials are closed to non-JWT staff for fifteen years from the date of creation.
Review Board materials may not be photocopied.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the Rare Book, Manuscript, and Special Collections Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files were received by the Rare Book, Manuscript, and Special Collections Library as transfers between 1987 and 2009.
Historical Note
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) evaluated its progress through a systematic study of the performance of its client accounts. Among the tools used to gauge the success of advertising campaigns and the health of ongoing client relationships were the compilation of account histories. The earliest surviving efforts by JWT to document its account relationships include approximately one hundred account histories collected from 1925-1926 by the Business Extension Department. The histories were prepared largely by Henry C. Miner, Jr. (JWT employee, 1925-1933) under the direction of Rae H. Smith (then a Representative and later Vice President and Director). From the 1920s through the 1940s, JWT New York Office's Department of Information and Records compiled records particularly on New York Office clients, including account histories, label and packaging designs and other printed materials. Beginning in the mid-1950s, the New York Office Information Center collected newspaper and magazine clippings, inter-office memoranda, research reports, and publications for various clients. This practice continued through the 1980s.
In addition to such institutional record-keeping practices, from the 1930s through the 1950s, individual staff members also compiled account records, which were then transferred to the Information Center of the New York Office. Howard Henderson, Vice President and Manager of the Cincinnati Office, gathered correspondence, memoranda, and reports regarding three clients: Chesebrough-Pond's, General Cigar Company, and the United States Playing Card Company. John Monsarrat, a JWT Executive Vice President and Director, provided material for the Chesebrough-Pond's account file. Another JWT Vice President, William C. McKeehan, provided further material about the United States Playing Card Company account in the 1950s.
Collection Overview
The JWT Account Files spans the years 1885-2008, with the bulk of materials covering 1920-1995. It is an artificially-created collection of information about client accounts held by the JWT and provides information about JWT's management of its advertising campaigns. Additionally, the files document deliberations about such topics as media selection; markets and marketing; and target audience for individual advertising campaigns. The bulk of the materials, especially the older records, document clients managed by JWT's New York Office, but the work of other offices is also represented, including: Atlanta Office (Marine Corps); Chicago Office (Oscar Mayer, Kraft); Detroit Office (Ford); and San Francisco Office (Sprint). The collection includes account histories; research reports; memoranda; correspondence; printed material; clippings; brochures and pamphlets; product labels and packaging designs; original artwork and advertising proofs; slides; photographs; audiocassettes and videocassettes. Clients represented include Eastman Kodak; Ford; Ford Dealer Association; R.T. French; General Cigar; Hamm's beer; Handy Andy; International Banana Association; IBM; Kellogg; Kraft; Quaker Oats; U.S. Marine Corps; US Sprint; Warner Lambert; White Castle; and the 1964 World's Fair. More limited materials are available for other significant JWT clients, including: Burger King; Champion Spark Plug; Domino's Pizza; Lever Brothers; Northern Telecom; Oscar Mayer; Rolex; Standard Brands; and Scott Paper.
Materials relating to client accounts for which only a limited amount of information is available are arranged into a Small Files Series. Following the Small Files, there are account records for thirty individual clients.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in other collections within the JWT archives, including
Advertising Vertical Files
Corporation Vertical Files
Howard Henderson Papers
Review Board Records
Advertisements produced for clients contained in the Account Files may be found in
Domestic Advertisements Collection
International Advertisements Collection
Photographs; Target marketing -- United States; Target marketing; Market surveys -- United States; Market surveys; Marketing -- United States -- History; Marketing; Advertising campaigns; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies; Audiocassettes; Proofs (printed matter); Slides (photographs); Videocassettes; Theo. Hamm Brewing Company; Standard Brands Incorporated; Scott Paper Company; R.T. French Company; White Castle (Restaurant); Warner-Lambert Company; US Sprint; United States. Marine Corps; General Cigar Company (Philadelphia, Pa.); Hyatt Hotels Corporation; International Business Machines Corporation; J. Walter Thompson Company -- History; Champion Spark Plug (Company); Domino's Pizza (Firm); Eastman Kodak Company; Ford Motor Company; Burger King Corporation; Northern Telecom Inc.; New York World's Fair (1964-1965); Quaker Oats Company; Oscar Mayer & Co; Kraft Foods Company; Kellogg Company; Montres Rolex S.A.; Lever Brothers Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. San Francisco Office; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Atlanta Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Detroit Office
- Small Accounts Files, 1885-2006 and undated, 55 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Consists of account-related materials for a large number of JWT clients for which very limited records exist. Includes account histories, research reports, clippings, correspondence, storyboards and printed material. Arranged alphabetically by company name.
  - A&M Karagheusian, account history, 1924-1926 (Box 1)
    [Business Extension Dept. report]
  - A. Beller and Company, account history, 1925 (Box 1)
  - A.C. Krumm and Son Macaroni Company, account history, 1926 (Box 1)
  - Abbot Laboratories, 1959, 1970-1980 (Box 1)
  - Absorbine Jr., storyboards, undated (Box 1)
  - Acemesa, clippings and press, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Act Media, brochure, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Activision, 1981-1984 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Council, general files, 1968 (Box 1)
  - A. J. Waffles, business review, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Akzo Salt, Consumer-Led New Product Development, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Alberto Culver, 1964-1971 (Box 1)
  - Alka-Z, case history, 1976 (Box 1)
  - All Sports, clippings and press, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Allegheny, correspondence and memoranda, 1978-1980, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Allied-Signal
    - Clippings and press, 1977-1986 (Box 1)
    - Signal World Magazine, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Almaden Vineyards, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - Aluminium Limited, 1959-1971 (Box 1)
  - Ambassador International, 1976-1979 (Box 1)
  - American Airlines, correspondence and memoranda, 1944 (Box 1)
  - American Bakeries, 1963-1966 (Box 1)
  - American-British Improvement Co., 1925-1926 (Box 1)
  - American Constructing Engineers Council, clippings and press, 1981 (Box 1)
  - American Equity, correspondence and memoranda, 1981 (Box 1)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), clippings and press, 1980 (Box 1)
  - American Film Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - American Gas and Electric Company, 1953 (Box 1)
  - American Gas Association (Box 2)
    - Communications Plans and Recommendations, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Ford's Theatre files, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Periodical, American Gas Association Monthly, 1984-1987, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - American Golf, memoranda, 1995 (Box 2)
  - American Home Products Corp., 1960-1967 (Box 2)
  - American Hospital Association, clippings and press, 1974 (Box 2)
  - American Machine and Foundry Co., 1966-1968 (Box 2)
  - American Oil Company (AMOCO), booklet - Bridge Score, 1935 (Box 2)
  - American Petroleum Institute, 1963-1971 (Box 2)
  - American Postal Workers Union, clippings and press, 1982-1985 (Box 2)
  - American Red Cross, booklet - Rhapsody in Red, 1994 (Box 2)
  - American Tobacco Company
    - General files, 1912 (Box 2)
    - Bull Durham print advertisement, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ameritech, clippings and press, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - Ames Department Store, brochure--More of What You're Shopping For, circa1986 (Box 2)
  - ANCO Wiper Blades
    - Media Plan, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Retail Ad Kit, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Anderson Company, clippings and press, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Andrew Jergens Company, 1916-1965
    - Account histories, 1916-1926 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence and histories, 1963-1965 (Box 3)
    - Howard Henderson files, 1930-1959 (Box 3)
    - Memoranda regarding Woodbury Slogan, 1946-1950 (Box 3)
    - Speech by Stanley Resor, 1920 (Box 3)
    - Story of Woodbury's Facial Soap, 1920-1951, 13 folders (Box 3)
  - Arbuckle Brothers (Yuban Coffee), 1912-1926, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Arrowhead Drinking Water, clippings and press, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Arts Foundation of Michigan, logos, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Associated Brewing Co., 1965-1968 (Box 3)
  - Association of American Playing Card Manufacturers, 1948, 1953-1960, 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Atlantic Cos., clippings and press, 1985 (Box 4)
  - AT&T, clippings and press, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Audio Devices, Inc., 1974 (Box 4)
  - Australian Tourist Commission
    - Agency Review, 1991 (Box 4)
    - Campaign Overview--Australia, the Feeling is Magic, circa 1993 (Box 4)
    - Credentials of North American Resources, circa1993 (Box 4)
    - JW Travelogue, circa 1993 (Box 4)
    - Meeting the Challenge of Asia, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Barclay House, memoranda, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Baskin Robbins, clippings and press, 1973-1985 (Box 4)
  - Bausch and Lomb
    - Company Analysis and Annual Report, 1977, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Magazine Advertising Estimates, 1981 (Box 4)
    - Printed material, 1970-1981 (Box 4)
  - Bay Area Cable Cooperative, clippings and press, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Beatrice Foods, clippings and press, 1960s-1980s, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Beecham Cosmetics (Vitabath), clippings and press, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Bell Atlantic, outdoor, undated (Box 4)
  - Bell South Mobility, clippings and press, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Bendix, clippings and press, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Benetton, clippings and press, 1983-1988 (Box 4)
  - [B.F. Goodrich, Legend of Chief Buffalo Child Long Lance: moved to Oversize Box 52] (Box 4)
  - B.F. Goodrich Footwear Co., brand policies, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Big Sky of Montana, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Bishopric Manufacturing Co., 1926 (Box 4)
  - Blockbuster, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Blue Chip Stamp Co., 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - Blue Cross and Blue Shield (Box 5)
    - General files,1962-1967, 1975, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Clippings and press, 1964-1986, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Publications, circa 1960-1983 (Box 5)
  - Book-of-the-Month-Club, printed material, 1976-1985 (Box 5)
  - Booth Newspapers, clippings and press, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Bo Rics, clippings and press, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Bosch
    - Business Plan, 1988-1933 (Box 5)
    - Estimated Marketing Expenses, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Boston Globe, 1926 (Box 5)
  - Boyle-Midway, 1959-1960, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Boys Club of America, clippings, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Brillo Manufacturing Co., 1963-1967
    - Research reports, 1963-1967 (Box 5)
    - Review of 1962 and Recommendations for 1963, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Bristol-Myers Squibb, JWT Worldwide Agency Discussion, 1995 (Box 5)
  - British Airways, Worldwide Media Planning Guidelines, circa 1994 (Box 5)
  - British Telecom, campaign history, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Brown & Williamson Tobacco Corporation, clippings and press, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Buckeye Soda Products, 1926 (Box 5)
  - Builders Square (Box 6)
    - General files, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Agency Review, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Banners, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Clippings, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Print Campaigns, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Buitoni Foods Corp., 1957 (Box 6)
  - Burlington Railroad--Chicago (Burlington and Quincy), 1926 (Box 6)
  - Buxton, Inc., 1925-1926 (Box 6)
  - California Milk Advisory Board
    - Printed material, 1980-1981 (Box 6)
    - Scripts, 1980, 4 folders (Box 6)
  - California Raisin Advisory Board, 1961-1968 (Box 6)
  - Campbell-Taggart Bakeries, 1967-1973 (Box 7)
  - Canada Mink Breeders Association, Canada Majestic Mink, undated (Box 7)
  - Capitol Federal Savings, clippings and press, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Car Care Council, clippings and press, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Carhartt, Inc., clippings and press, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Carl's Jr., Situation Analysis, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Car Max, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - Carte Blanche, 1967-1972 (Box 7)
  - Carter's Ink Company, package design, 1929-1942, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Case, J.I.
    - Agriculture, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Building Tomorrow Together, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Clippings, 1987-1989 (Box 7)
    - Closer Working Relationship, undated (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
    - Deck originals, undated (Box 7)
    - Executive meeting, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Positioning, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 8)
    - Radio television reports, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Research, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Vision Quest, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Why Case Is A Good Prospect, undated (Box 8)
  - Castle and Cooke, 1981-1986 (Box 8)
  - Celotex Company, 1924-1925 (Box 8)
  - Charles W. Breneman Co., 1925 (Box 8)
  - Charles William Stores, circa 1920 (Box 8)
  - Chatham, 1972-1979
    - Legal department, 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Printed material, 1974-1979 (Box 8)
    - Profile, 1975, 4 folders (Box 8)
    - Scripts, 1977-1978, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Cheek-Neal Coffee Company (Maxwell House coffee), 1925 (Box 9)
  - Chelmsford Ginger-Ale Co., 1924 (Box 9)
  - Chemical Bank
    - General files, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
    - Multinational Media Proposal, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Organizational Changes, wholesale banking, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Proposed Media Strategy, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Chemical Manufacturers Association, clippings and press, 1979-1983 (Box 9)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's, Inc., 1885-1980 and undated
    - Account histories, 1923-1964, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Advertisement schedules, 1885-1909, 1914-1916 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, memoranda and reports, 1940-1970 and undated, 9 folders (Box 10)
    - Howard Henderson papers
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1951-1955, 8 folders (Box 10)
      - Reports on Angel Skin, 1953, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - John Monsarrat papers, 1955-1956 (Box 10)
      [Includes Correspondence and memoranda]
    - Marketing plans, 1957-1958 (Box 10)
    - Package design, 1907-1952, 8 folders (Box 10)
    - Package design, 1907-1952, 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Printed material
      - Brochures, 1958-circa 1960 (Box 11)
      - Newspapers and magazine clippings, 1946-1980 (Box 11)
    - Reports
      - Competitive new product announcements, 1969 (Box 11)
      - Consumer purchase panel, 1956 (Box 11)
      - Major multiple store buyers, 1956 (Box 11)
      - Media recommendations, 1956 (Box 11)
      - New product suggestions and additives, 1956 (Box 11)
      - Report of Investigation, 1933, 1978 (Box 11)
      - Study of Pond's television advertising, 1953 (Box 11)
      - Summary of Pond's advertising, 1956 (Box 11)
  - Chevron
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
    - Retail Advertising Campaign, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Chichester Pills, correspondence, 1911-1977 (Box 11)
  - Christian Dior, 1977-1985 (Box 11)
  - Church and Dwight Co., Inc., printed material, 1946 (Box 11)
  - Circle Line Sightseeing Yachts, clippings and press, 1985-1987 (Box 11)
  - City Baking Co., account history, 1924 (Box 11)
  - [Citibank, What We Are Learning, 1996: Moved to Restricted Materials Box 49] (Box 11)
  - Clairol, presentation, Building a Global Brand, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Colgate-Palmolive, report--AJAX, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Colman, J&J: See J&J Colman (Box 12)
  - Columbia Gas System Inc., printed material, 1978-1979 (Box 12)
  - Computerland
    - Marketing Manual, 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Printed material, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Proposal for Awareness and Attitude Study Among Computerland Prime Prospects Living in the Bay Area, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Congoleum-Nairns, Inc., printed material, 1961-1979 (Box 12)
  - Coors, printed material, 1978-1984 (Box 12)
  - Corning Glass Works, 1917-1925 (Box 12)
  - Corticelli Silk Co., account history, 1925 (Box 12)
  - Costa Cruises, printed material, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Cranbrook Institute, clippings and press, circa 1966 (Box 12)
  - Cream of Wheat Corp., account history, 1926-1987 (Box 12)
  - Credit Union National Association, clippings and press, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Crowell Publishing Co., investigation and printed material, 1925 (Box 12)
  - Culver, Alberto: See Alberto Culver (Box 12)
  - Curtice Brothers Co., account history, 1926 (Box 12)
  - Cutter Laboratories, clippings and press, 1974-1978 (Box 12)
  - Daewoo, clippings and press, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Dart & Craft, clipping, undated (Box 12)
  - Davey Tree Expert Co., account history, 1925 (Box 12)
  - Dean Witter and Company
    - Action Steps, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Active Assets client package, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Active Assets prospects package, 1984 (Box 12)
    - ATM correspondence, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Billing, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
    - Budget and Scheduling Alternatives, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Conference reports, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Estimate file, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Instant Cash client package, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Intercapital Prospect Card, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Intercapital Prospect Lease Generation, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Intercapital Prospect VISA Offer, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Intercapital VISA, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Lead Generation, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Memoranda, 1984, 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous files, 1984-1985 (Box 14)
    - Money Market Fund, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Presentations, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Printed material, 1962-1965 (Box 14)
    - Prospectus trimming, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Reference guide, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Sales package to branches, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Sears Savings Bank, 1984
      - ATM Offer (Box 14)
      - Prospects (Box 14)
      - VISA card (Box 14)
    - T.O.S., 1985 (Box 14)
  - DeBeers1977-2000
    [Other items in Oversize Materials.]
    - [Activities in Japan booklet, 1996: Moved to Restricted Materials Box 49], 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Clippings and press, 1978-2000, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - How JWT Changed to Mating Ritual in Japan, circa 1993 (Box 15)
    - Printed material, undated (Box 15)
    - Promotional, 1993 (Box 15)
    - Strategy Considerations for 1978, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Supervisors conference, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Del Ray Corporation, package Design, 1933 (Box 15)
  - Del Webb Development Company, clippings and press, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Dentcare Systems, clippings and press, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
  - Denver International Children's Festival, logo, undated (Box 15)
  - Detroit Sailing Grand Prix
    - Guests, press, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Master files, I-V, 1982-1986, 6 folders (Box 15)
    - Menus, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
    - Participants, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Detroit Symphony, logos, undated (Box 16)
  - DeVilbliss Co., printed material, 1976-1979 (Box 16)
  - Diamond Salt Co., 1926? (Box 16)
  - Diet Center, clippings and press, 1981-1986 (Box 16)
  - Dior, Christian: See Christian Dior (Box 16)
  - Discover America, Inc., printed material, 1967-1968 (Box 16)
  - Disney: See Walt Disney Productions (Box 16)
  - Dollar Rent-a-Car, printed material, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Dolly Madison Baking Corp., account history, 1926 (Box 16)
  - Domtar Gypsum, production reports, 1989 (Box 16)
  - Douglas Pectin Company (Certo), account history, 1924-1925 (Box 16)
  - Dunlop, clippings and press, 1980-1984 (Box 16)
  - Dwight Manufacturing Company, account history, 1926 (Box 16)
  - Dymo Visual Systems (Esselte), clippings and press, 1976-1979 (Box 16)
  - Eaton
    - Clippings and press, 1969-1985 (Box 16)
    - Corporate identification, undated (Box 16)
    - Publications, 1969-1976 (Box 16)
  - Eberhard Faber Pencil Company, 1932 (Box 16)
  - Eckerd Drug Company, clippings and press, 1977-1985 (Box 16)
  - Economic Development Corporation
    - Brochure, 1988 (Box 16)
    - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 16)
    - Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 16)
    - Creative, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Early Marketing Development, 1987 (Box 16)
    - Job Orders, 1988, folders 1-2 of 3 (Box 16)
    - Job Orders, 1988 (continued), folder 3 of 3 (Box 17)
    - Letters of terms, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Marketing plans
      - General files, 1987 (Box 17)
      - Communications plans, 1987-1988 (Box 17)
      - Developing a Marketing Strategy for San Francisco, 1987 (Box 17)
      - Towards a Marketing Plan for the City of San Francisco, 1987 (Box 17)
    - Media, 1987-1988 (Box 17)
    - Meetings
      - General, 1988 (Box 17)
      - Board meetings, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Press, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Printed material
      - Getting Things Done: Visions and Goals for San Francisco, undated (Box 17)